Nephew, you're here.
And Mei girl came along too.
Uncle Qi.
Come, have a seat.
Why did you call me here?
Nephew.
Your situation in the Sheng Family,
I've heard a little about it.
Must be tough.
For an outsider to gain a foothold there,
is nearly impossible.
Bullshit.
What do you mean?
Keep spouting bullshit.
You...
I just mean well.
I can give you a chance.
Thirty li west of here,
Black Wind Ridge's Sleeping Moon Valley.
It holds an ancient sacrificial pit.
The pit isn't big,
but I hear it holds lots of good stuff.
Our Qi Family
has never had the time to deal with it.
If you're willing,
I can provide you with a map.
And I can tell you the entrance.
As long as you can bring something out,
I might share what happened 20 years ago.
I know.
I know about it.
Isn't Old Master Qi talking about
where those who return lose their voices,
the Mute Pit?
Rumors.
Those are pure rumors.
It's just hearsay.
It might be a little bit dangerous,
but wealth is found in danger.
Right?
If you bring out one or two Grave goods,
Not only in the Sheng Family
will you gain prestige,
but in our Qi Family,
we will also owe you a favor.
It's killing two birds with one stone.
Besides, as far as I know,
The dragon-seeking Zhang family,
someone from their lineage
might have been there too.
Does this old geezer want me buried there?
If you go,
I'll make sure you're buried there,
and never come out.
Give me the map.
Alright.
How decisive.
Uncle Qi.
By the order of the family head,
I must protect Zhang Tianyou's safety.
I will go with him.
That's wonderful.
With Miss Mei as his escort,
I couldn't ask for more!
Young Master.
I think this place is a bit...
a bit eerie.
I've explored tombs for half my life,
and I've never seen a place this clean.
There's not a single ant on the ground.
The air has a sweet, bloody scent.
Like rotting flowers mixed with rust.
It's not rust.
The soil is black
and has a bloody stench.
It's Corpse-blood soil.
More than one or two people died here.
Qi Lianhai wants me to die here.
Or maybe this is just...
a test.
What test?
To test who I am.
To see if I can handle the Tidal Tomb.
Let's go. Hurry up!
Wait.
It's fine.
Let's go.
Who's chasing me?
Who's chasing me?!
Someone is chasing me!
There's no one.
No, didn't you hear that?
Look.
It's an echo.
An echo?
There's constant geological pressure,
causing underground water vibrations.
Focus!
I... I'm wide awake.
Alright, alright.
Give me one! Give me one!
How is it?
I'm good, I'm good.
This thing of yours works great!
Better than a black donkey hoof.
Looks like you came well-prepared.
I said, you came well-prepared.
Alright, alright. Let's go.
What is this place?
Young Master.
Are these the people who came before us?
This looks like a sacrificial pit.
It's not a sacrificial pit.
This is a stomach.
A stomach that can swallow people alive.
I can't cut it!
Zhang Tianyou!
Think of something!
What do we do?
Why isn't it attacking you?
It's the Zhang family's evil-warding lock.
Got it.
Chant with me.
Chant what?
Come on.
Zhang Tianyou.
Let's go.
Dead end.
What is this thing?
Is this...
...an illusion?
It's not an illusion. It's a memory.
He seems to be retracing his final steps.
Let's go. Follow him.
Let's go.
Come on.
Brother Shu!
Watch out!
That bastard Qi Lianhai...
He obviously sent us here to die!
Do you recognize this thing?
Father.
Were you here twenty years ago too?
Talisman, Curse, Seal, and Eye.
I'm so close to gathering everything.